Brandyn Coverdill

IT Support Technician

brandyncoverdill98@gmail.com 319-360-9465

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/brandyn-coverdill/

IT Support Technician with over a year of experience in Desktop Support, including using ServiceNow for helpdesk tickets to resolve issues for employees.

Mapped, inventoried and renamed thousands of computers using Visio. Inventoried, managed and setup hardware to employee workstations. Worked with and managed a team of IT professionals to help with Epic implementation.

Key Skills

- Languages: C#, Java, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, some Python.
- Technologies: ASP.NET MVC, WPF, Windows Forms, JSP, Servlets, Microsoft SQL, MySQL, Stored Procedures, jQuery, Git Bath, Jira. Regex, Selenium 3, Selenium WebDriver.
- IDEs / Editors: Visual Studio, NetBeats, Notepad++, SQL Workbench, SQL Management Studio, Brackets, Atom, Visio, Microsft Office.

Professional Experience

Desktop Support

Kootenai Health | February 2021 - June 2022

- Inventoried, renamed and mapped over 2,000 computers and printers in a hospital on/off regular working hours with Visio
- · Experienced with ServiceNow for helpdesk tickets.
- Managed and worked with a team of MultiCare IT professionals to help with our hospital's transition from Meditech to Epic.
- Reimaged computers to deploy to areas in the hospital.
- Inventoried over a few thousand devices and peripheral hardware to assemble through the hospital and nearby clinics.

Capstone Project

Kirkwood Community College | October 2020 - December 2020

- Worked as a scrum team that created a pseudo pet adoption website with a retail desktop application.
- Strong understanding of OOP foundations (Inheritance, Polymorphism, Abstraction, Encapsulation).
- Designing projects with documentation.
- Experienced working from home during Covid-19.
- Commited on project through GitHub.
- · Used Jira for issues and bugs during sprints.

Education

Computer Software Development Kirkwood Communiy College at Cedar Rapids, IA| 2018 - 2020

Certifications

Java Programming December 2020

.NET Programming (C#)
December 2020